SEPTIANATA RIZKY PRATAMA

Full-stack Developer

Sleman, DI Yogyakarta I Email: ian.rizkypratama@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a full-stack developer with over 5 years of experience, proficient in Java, PHP, and JavaScript. Expert in developing web applications and REST APIs using Laravel, Express.js, and Next.js. Recently completed a successful project: nossa.co.id and www.artopologi.com. Really excited to learn new things and enjoy collaborating and working together as a team.

EXPERIENCE

Nossa - Jakarta, Indonesia

Full-stack Developer - Remote (August 2024 - present)

- Developed web applications to manage community membership platforms using Laravel and Vue.js.
- Designed and implemented database designs using MySQL.

Artopologi - Jakarta, Indonesia

Full-stack Developer – Remote (July 2022 – present)

- Developed REST API applications to manage e-commerce platforms using Express.js on Node.js.
- Developed web applications as the main interface for whole user using Next.js on Node.js.
- · Designed and implemented database designs using MySQL.
- · Prepared API documentation using Postman and OpenAPI.

Remote Worker Indonesia – Yogyakarta, Indonesia

JavaScript Mentor - Remote (May 2023 - saat ini)

- Developed a roadmap for beginners to become backend developers.
- Created tutorial materials in video and text formats based on the roadmap, covering topics like JavaScript, Git, Node.js, and more.
- Conducted live coding sessions for discussions and Q&A with members on the material.

Beone Optima Solusi - Tangerang, Indonesia

Backend Developer – Remote (October 2021 – May 2022)

- Developed bridging applications to connect existing backends with mobile applications using Express.is.
- Developed backend applications for handling human resources using Laravel.

Timedoor Indonesia – Bali, Indonesia

Backend Developer – Onsite (November 2018 – November 2021)

- Developed full-stack applications to manage e-commerce platforms using Laravel and MySQL.
- Developed REST API applications to manage water billing systems using Laravel and PostgreSQL.

EDUCATION

ITB STIKOM Bali (2018 - 2020)

B.Sc. in Information Systems - GPA: 3.78

Politeknik Negeri Bali (2014 - 2017)

Diploma in Informatics Management - GPA: 3.81

SKILLS

- PHP (Laravel)
- JavaScript (Express.js, ElysiaJS, Next.js, Vue.js)
- Git
- MySQL, PostgreSQL
- OpenAPI